<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Ramblings on Molly&#39;s Cafe ☕</title>
    <link>https://molly.cafe/categories/ramblings/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Ramblings on Molly&#39;s Cafe ☕</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 12 Jan 2025 01:13:04 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://molly.cafe/categories/ramblings/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>So much shit to do.</title>
      <link>https://molly.cafe/posts/too_many_ideas/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jan 2025 01:13:04 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://molly.cafe/posts/too_many_ideas/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Good now, Merry Christmas, and happy new year! I know it&amp;rsquo;s been a while; that&amp;rsquo;s on me. I&amp;rsquo;m a little bit of a dumbass and forgot I had a site for a good month or so.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Anyway, hi again. I want to talk about something that&amp;rsquo;s been making it a little harder to post as of late: terrible time management and me picking up several things at once.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I have a very active imagination. Lots of shit I want to do, and even more ideas every day, and I even write a large majority of them down in a notebook I keep to myself. But I don&amp;rsquo;t always have the energy, money, or time to actually do much with all of those ideas, and when I do go through with them, I fail to manage my time well. So here I&amp;rsquo;m going to talk about a few of the small projects I&amp;rsquo;ve started and things I&amp;rsquo;ve picked up.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The importance of game modding</title>
      <link>https://molly.cafe/posts/the_importance_of_game_modding/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2024 20:20:54 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://molly.cafe/posts/the_importance_of_game_modding/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Game modding has been a part of video games for decades. From small changes to creating entirely new level designs, it&amp;rsquo;s been a way for players to take their favorite games into their own hands and change them however they&amp;rsquo;d like, whether that be for better or for worse. (&lt;em&gt;Usually worse.&lt;/em&gt;)&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Game modding also holds significant importance across the video gaming industry, and within the gaming community as a whole.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
